JOSEPH E. PERSICO PAPERS (APAP030) 1910-2003
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
1971 May 14 New York City, NY, Excerpts, New York State Council on the Arts Awards Ceremony
1971 May 20 Albany, NY, Meeting with New York City Delegation
1971 May 24 Albany, NY, Meeting with New York City Delegation to Congress
1971 May 24 Albany, NY, Statement by Rockefeller
1971 May 26 Huntington, NY, Remarks, Suffolk Republican Committee
1971 May 28 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Rent De-Control laws
1971 June 2 New York City, NY, Remarks, Labor Reception
1971 June 10 New York City, NY, Interview, before New York State Republican Committee Dinner at Hilton Hotel
1971 June 10 New York City, NY, Remarks, New York State Republican Committee Dinner at Hilton Hotel
1971 June 10 New York City, NY, Remarks, New York State Republican Committee Dinner at Waldorf Astoria
1971 June 10 New York City, NY, Excerpts, New York State Republican Committee Dinner at Waldorf Astoria
1971 June 11 Rome, NY, Remarks, Wright Park Manor Ribbon Cutting
1971 June 11 Rome, NY, Excerpts, Wright Park Manor Ribbon Cutting
1971 June 11 Utica, NY, Press Conference, 20th Anniversary of Rome Air Development Center
1971 June 11 Utica, NY, Remarks, 20th Anniversary of Rome Air Development Center
1971 June 11 Utica, NY, Excerpts, 20th Anniversary of Rome Air Development Center
1971 June 15 Washington, D.C., TV Interview, with Bernard Kalb CBS
1971 June 15 Washington, D.C., Press Interview, Ways and Means Committee
1971 June 15 Washington, D.C., Excerpts, Ways and Means Committee
1971 June 16 Garden City, NY, Remarks, Nassau County Republican Committee
1971 June 18 Rochester, NY, Press Release, President Nixon and Rockefeller on Revenue Sharing
1971 June 18 Rochester, NY, Excerpts, President Nixon and Rockefeller on Revenue Sharing
1971 June 23 New York City, NY, Interview, with Frank Lynn
1971 June 23 Rochester, NY, Address, National Newspaper Association
1971 June 23 Rochester, NY, Excerpts, National Newspaper Association
1971 July 5 New York City, NY, Excerpts, American Bar Association Annual Meeting
1971 July 15 Brooklyn, NY, Remarks, Groundbreaking Regina Pacis Residence
1971 July 15 Brooklyn, NY, Excerpts, Groundbreaking Regina Pacis Residence
1971 July 15 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Battery Park Construction Site
1971 July 22 Glens Falls, NY, Remarks, New York Building and Construction Trades Council
1971 July 23 Washington, D.C., Address, National Tax Association Seminar
1971 July 23 Washington, D.C., Excerpts, National Tax Association Seminar
1971 July 23 Denver, CO, Republican National Committee
1971 July 23 Denver, CO, Excerpts, Republican National Committee
1971 July 28 Washington, D.C., Public Works Committee of US House of Representatives
1971 July 28 Washington, D.C., Statement for Release, Public Works Committee of US House of Representatives
1971 August 3 Washington, D.C., Testimony at Senator Muskie's Hearing
1971 August 3 Washington, D.C., Statement of Release, Before Subcommittee on Intergovernmental Relations of the Committee on Governmental Operations
1971 August 19 New York City, NY, Press Conference, New York City Commission
1971 August 31 Colorado Springs, CO, Meet the Press, NBC
1971 August 31 Colorado Springs, CO, Meet the Press, NBC
1971 September 8 New York City, NY, Remarks, Labor College
1971 September 16 Monticello, NY, Address, County Officers Association
1971 September 17 Attica, NY, Statement, by Walter Dunbar Executive Commissioner New York State Correctional Services
1971 September 21 New York City, NY, Press Conference, American Association of Motor Vehicles
1971 September 21 New York City, NY, Remarks, American Association of Motor Vehicles
1971 September 21 New York City, NY, Excerpts, American Association of Motor Vehicles
1971 September 21 New York City, NY, Excerpts, International Downtown Executives Luncheon
1971 September 23 Lake Placid, NY, Remarks, New York State Conservation Council
1971 September 23 Lake Placid, NY, Excerpts, New York State Conservation Council
1971 September 24 Albany, NY, Remarks, Schuyler Mansion
1971 September 24 Albany, NY, Remarks, New York State Bar Association
1971 September 24 Albany, NY, Excerpts, New York State Bar Association
1971 September 24 Albany, NY, Q and A Session, following New York State Bar Association
1971 September 28 Long Island, NY, Press Interview, Association of Commerce and Industry
1971 September 28 Long Island, NY, Excerpts, Association of Commerce and Industry
1971 September 29 Painted Post, NY, Excerpts, Route 17 Association Luncheon
1971 September 29 Jamestown, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of Jamestown City Hall
1971 October 9 New York City, NY, Tribute to Italian Americans
1971 October 9 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Columbus Day Dinner
1971 October 12 Washington, D.C., Press Conference, following Meeting with Congressional Delegation
1971 October 13 New York City, NY, Remarks, Knickerbocker Hospital
1971 October 13 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Knickerbocker Hospital
1971 October 13 New York City, NY, Martha Deanne Show
1971 October 13 New York City, NY, Press Interview, following Martha Deanne Show
1971 October 14 New York City, NY, Remarks, Cerebral Palsy Association
1971 October 14 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Cerebral Palsy Association
1971 October 19 New York City, NY, Remarks, New York State United Nations Day Observance
1971 October 19 New York City, NY, Press Interview, following New York State United Nations Day Observance
1971 October 19 New York City, NY, Excerpts, New York State United Nations Day Observance
1971 October 20 New York City, NY, Remarks, before 26th Annual Al Smith Memorial Dinner
1971 October 20 New York City, NY, Excerpts, 26th Annual Al Smith Memorial Dinner
1971 October 21 Ticonderoga, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of International Paper Co. Plant
1971 October 26 Tarrytown, NY, Remarks, Westchester County Association
1971 October 26 Tarrytown, NY, Press Interview, Bond Issue, Tarrytown Bypass
1971 October 26 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Bond Issue, Wagner as Chairman of Citizens Committee
1971 October 27 New York City, NY, Statement of Rockefeller, delivered by Environmental Conservation Commissioner
1971 October 28 Syracuse, NY, Excerpts, Syracuse Chamber of Commerce
1971 October 28 Queens, NY, Excerpts, Inspection Tour of East River Transit Tunnel
1971 October 29 New York City, NY, Excerpts, United Teachers of New York Press Conference
1971 November 3 New York City, NY, Remarks, American Jewish Committee Appeal for Human Relations
1971 November 3 New York City, NY, Excerpts, American Jewish Committee Appeal for Human Relations
1971 November 9 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Salute to President Nixon Dinner
1971 November 10 New York City, NY, Address, Conference on Alcohol Problems
1971 November 10 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Conference on Alcohol Problems
1971 November 12 Syracuse, NY, Remarks, Association of Council Members and SUNY College Trustees
1971 November 12 Syracuse, NY, Excerpts, Association of Council Members and SUNY College Trustees
1971 November 15 New York City, NY, Memorial Tribute for M. Switzer
1971 November 16 New York City, NY, Remarks, New York State Traffic Safety Council
1971 November 16 New York City, NY, Excerpts, New York State Traffic Safety Council
1971 November 16 Brookhaven, LI, Excerpts, Brookhaven Park Site Transfer
1971 November 20 Tarrytown, NY, Remarks, New York State Environmental Workshop
1971 November 20 Tarrytown, NY, Q and A Session, following New York State Environmental Workshop
1971 November 20 Tarrytown, NY, Excerpts, New York State Environmental Workshop
1971 November 21 Albany, NY, Statement, Tarrytown Bypass
1971 November 22 New York City, NY, Press Interview, New York State Psychiatric Institute
1971 November 22 New York City, NY, Excerpts, New York State Psychiatric Institute
1971 November 23 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Senator Brydges and County Executives
1971 November 27 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Meeting of Legislative Leaders
1971 November 30 New York City, NY, Remarks, New York State Committee for Children
1971 November 30 New York City, NY, Press Interview, New York State Committee for Children
1971 December 3 New York City, NY, Meeting of Congressional Delegation
1971 December 9 Washington, D.C., Press Interview, before Rockefeller's Testimony for Blatnik Committee
1971 December 9 Washington, D.C., Rockefeller's Testimony for Blatnik Committee
1971 December 15 New York City, NY, Eulogy, Given by Rockefeller for David Sarnoff
1971 December 15 Albany, NY, News Conference, in Red Room at State Capitol
1971 December 20 New York City, NY, TV Interview, with Gabe Ressman of WNBC
1971 December 21 New York City, NY, Statement, at Press Conference on No-Fault Auto Insurance
1971 December 28 Albany, NY, Remarks, New York State Council of Agriculture
1971 December 30 Albany, NY, Press Interview, Outside Senator Brydges Office
1971 December 31 Albany, NY, Press Interview, Outside Senator Brydges Office
1972
1972 January 11 Albany, NY, Address, Albany Chamber of Commerce
1972 January 14 Albany, NY, Press Interview, Budget Briefing
1972 January 17 Albany, NY, Remarks, New York State Veterans of Foreign Wars
1972 January 18 Rochester, NY, Remarks, Tribute to Gordan Howe Flagship Ballroom
1972 January 18 Rochester, NY, Remarks, Tribute to Gordan Howe Holiday Inn Ballroom
1972 January 23 Tarrytown, NY, Remarks, Groundbreaking Pocantico Central Schools
1972 January 23 Tarrytown, NY, Excerpts, Groundbreaking Pocantico Central Schools
1972 January 25 New York City, NY, Remarks, Testimony for Victor Borella
1972 February 1 Albany, NY, Remarks, New York State Women's Legislative Forum
1972 February 1 Albany, NY, Q and A Session, following New York State Women's Legislative Forum
1972 February 10 New York City, NY, Remarks, United Jewish Appeal Dinner
1972 February 10 New York City, NY, Q and A Session, following United Jewish Appeal Dinner
1972 February 12 Brooklyn, NY, Remarks, Kings County Republican Committee
1972 February 12 New York City, NY, Press Interview, before New York County Republican Dinner
1972 February 12 New York City, NY, Press Interview, following New York County Republican Dinner
1972 February 17 New York City, NY, Remarks, Building Industries Boy Scout Lunch-o-ree
1972 February 17 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Building Industries Boy Scout Lunch-o-ree
1972 February 28 Albany, NY, Remarks, New York State Council of Churches
1972 March 1 Albany, NY, Testimony at Joint Legislative Committee on Insurance
1972 March 1 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Testimony at Joint Legislative Committee on Insurance
1972 March 3 Manchester, NH, Statement, Rally for Re-election of President Nixon
1972 March 6 Albany, NY, Remarks, Annual Teenage Republican Meeting
1972 March 6 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Annual Teenage Republican Meeting
1972 March 6 Albany, NY, Q and A Session, following Annual Teenage Republican Meeting
1972 March 7 Albany, NY, Remarks, New York State League of Voters Conference
1972 March 7 Albany, NY, Excerpts, New York State League of Voters Conference
1972 March 7 Albany, NY, Press Interview, following New York State League of Voters Conference
1972 March 7 Albany, NY, Remarks, New York State Broadcasters Association
1972 March 7 Albany, NY, Remarks, United Parents Association
1972 March 16 New York City, NY, Remark, National Credit and Commercial Conference
1972 March 16 New York City, NY, Press Interview, following National Credit and Commercial Conference
1972 March 20 New York City, NY, Meeting with Nixon on Drugs
1972 March 20 New York City, NY, Press Interview, Meeting with Nixon on Drugs
1972 March 21 Albany, NY, News Conference, Red Room at Capital
1972 March 21 New York City, NY, Remarks, United Jewish Appeal Annual Inaugural Dinner
1972 March 21 New York City, NY, Excerpts, United Jewish Appeal Annual Inaugural Dinner
1972 March 22 Albany, NY, Interview, Budget
1972 March 22 Albany, NY, New York State Farm Bureau
1972 April 3 New York City, NY, News Conference, Judges for the Court of Appeals
1972 April 12 New York City, NY, Excerpts, FDR Four Freedoms Award Dinner
1972 April 19 Albany, NY, Announcement, Federal Assistance to New York State
1972 April 21 Albany, NY, Remarks, Environmental Teach-in
1972 April 21 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Environmental Teach-in
1972 April 21 Albany, NY, Press Interview, following Environmental Teach-in
1972 April 24 Albany, NY, Remarks, Dedication of Appellate Division Courts and Chambers
1972 May 1 New York City, NY, Remarks, Citizens Budget Committee
1972 May 1 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Citizens Budget Committee
1972 May 3 Hyde Park, NY, Remarks, Dedication of Eleanor Roosevelt Wings of FDR Library
1972 May 3 Hyde Park, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of Eleanor Roosevelt Wings of FDR Library
1972 May 11 Portland, OR, Salute to the President
1972 May 11 Portland, OR, Press Interview, at Portland Airport
1972 May 12 San Francisco, CA, Excerpts, Commonwealth Club Luncheon
1972 May 15 Albany, NY, Statement, Preceding Press Conference at Red Room
1972 May 16 New York City, NY, Remarks, Convention of the International Union of Dolls, Toys, etc.
1972 May 16 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Convention of the International Union of Dolls, Toys, etc.
1972 May 25 New York City, NY, New York State Council on the Arts Award Presentations
1972 May 25 New York City, NY, Excerpts, New York State Council on the Arts Award Presentations
1972 May 25 New York City, NY, Remarks, Catholic Interracial Council
1972 May 25 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Catholic Interracial Council
1972 May 26 New York City, NY, Swearing-in of Frank Rossetti
1972 May 26 New York City, NY, Interview, with TASS
1972 May 26 New York City, NY, Swearing-in of Stephen Gottliel
1972 May 31 New York City, NY, Bill Signing for Environmental Improvement
1972 May 31 New York City, NY, Press Interview, with William Farrell and Frank Lynn
1972 May 31 New York City, NY, Swearing-in of Annie B. Martin
1972 June 7 Rock Point, RI, Press Conference, Rockefeller and Ron Chafee
1972 June 7 Providence, RI, Remarks, Rally for Chafee
1972 June 8 New York City, NY, Remarks, Republican State Committee Luncheon
1972 June 8 New York City, NY, Remarks, Republican State Committee Dinner
1972 June 13 New York City, NY, New York State Historic Trust Museum of Modern Art
1972 June 13 New York City, NY, Excerpts, New York State Historic Trust Museum of Modern Art
1972 June 13 Brooklyn, NY, Remarks, Council of Jewish Women
1972 June 14 New York City, NY, Remarks, Safety Poster Contest Winners
1972 June 14 New York City, NY, Press Interview, with Jack Allen WOR Radio
1972 June 14 New York City, NY, Remarks, Scholastic Achievement Dinner
1972 June 19 New York City, NY, Remarks, International Leather Goods, Plastics and Novelty Workers Convention
1972 June 19 New York City, NY, Excerpts, International Leather Goods, Plastics and Novelty Workers Convention
1972 June 21 Albany, NY, Remarks, Don Wickham Retirement Dinner
1972 June 21 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Don Wickham Retirement Dinner
1972 July 5 Albany, NY, Remarks, New York State Republican Committee Meeting
1972 July 5 Albany, NY, Excerpts, New York State Republican Committee Meeting
1972 July 10 New York City, NY, Swearing-in of Martin Ginsberg
1972 July 10 New York City, NY, TV Interview, Gabe Pressman WNEW
1972 July 18 Cooperstown, NY, Remarks, New York State Broadcasting Association
1972 July 19 White Plains, NY, Remarks, John Peter Zinger Chapter of Sigma Delta Chi
1972 July 19 White Plains, NY, Press Interview, John Peter Zinger Chapter of Sigma Delta Chi
1972 July 26 New York City, NY, Press Conference, New York Committee to Re-Elect the President
1972 July 27 New York City, NY, Interview, with Bill Kennedy
1972 August 15 Jamaica, NY, Remarks, Archer Ave. Groundbreaking Ceremony
1972 August 15 Jamaica, NY, Excerpts, Archer Ave. Groundbreaking Ceremony
1972 August 17 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Regarding Teamsters Endorsement of Nixon
1972 August 17 New York City, NY, Press Interview, following Teamsters Endorsement of Nixon
1972 September 6 Kiamesha Lake, NY, Remarks, AFL-CIO Constitutional Convention
1972 September 6 Kiamesha Lake, NY, Excerpts, AFL-CIO Constitutional Convention
1972 September 10 St. Louis, IL, Excerpts, Governor Ogilvie Testimonial Dinner
1972 September 12 Flushing, NY, Remarks, Honoring Commissioner Louis Levine
1972 September 12 Electchester, NY, Excerpts, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers
1972 September 13 St Louis, MO, Excerpts, Fund Raising Dinner for Kit Bond
1972 September 14 Tannersville, NY, Remarks, Policemen's Benevolent Association
1972 September 14 Tannersville, NY, Excerpts, Policemen's Benevolent Association
1972 September 14 New York City, NY, Remarks, Party for Sol Wachtler
1972 September 14 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Memorial Service for Aline Saarinen
1972 September 15 New York City, NY, Remarks, Rockford County Republican Committee
1972 September 15 New York City, NY, Q and A Session, following Rockford County Republican Committee
1972 September 15 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Rockford County Republican Committee
1972 September 16 Flushing, NY, Excerpts, Storefront Opening
1972 September 20 New York City, NY, Martha Deane Show WOR
1972 September 20 New York City, NY, Press Interview, following Martha Deane Show WOR
1972 September 25 New York City, NY, Police Conference of New York Endorsing Nixon
1972 September 26 JFK Airport, Remarks, Israel's Anniversary
1972 September 26 JFK Airport, Excerpts, Israel's Anniversary
1972 September 27 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Meeting of Nixon and Labor Leaders
1972 October 2 New York City, NY, Remarks, Physicians Associates Presentation of Certificates
1972 October 3 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Annual Convention of County Officers Association
1972 October 4 New York City, NY, Press Interview, Hispanic Endorsement of Nixon
1972 October 4 New York City, NY, Hispanic Endorsement of Nixon
1972 October 4 New Haven, CT, Excerpts, Connecticut, Fund Raising Dinner
1972 October 7 New York City, NY, Remarks, Peter J. Brennan Testimonial Dinner
1972 October 7 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Peter J. Brennan Testimonial Dinner
1972 October 7 New York City, NY, Remarks, Americans of Ukrainian Descent
1972 October 7 New York City, NY, Remarks, Pulaski Memorial
1972 October 10 Welfare Island, NY, Remarks, East 63rd St. Tunnel
1972 October 10 Welfare Island, NY, Press Interview, East 63rd St. Tunnel
1972 October 10 Wilmington, DE, Remarks, Peterson Haskell Rally
1972 October 10 Wilmington, DE, Press Interview, after Peterson Haskell Rally
1972 October 10 Wilmington, DE, Excerpts, Peterson Haskell Rally
1972 October 10 Wilmington, DE, Press Interview, Rockefeller and Governor Peterson
1972 October 10 Wilmington, DE, Remarks, Senior Citizens Reception
1972 October 10 Wilmington, DE, Excerpts, Senior Citizens Reception
1972 October 10 Wilmington, DE, Remarks, Podua Academy Student Assembly
1972 October 10 Wilmington, DE, Excerpts, Podua Academy Student Assembly
1972 October 11 New York City, NY, Press Conference, New York Democrats for Nixon
1972 October 11 New York City, NY, Press Interview, after New York Democrats for Nixon
1972 October 16 Camp Hill, PA, Press Conference, Cumberland County Republican Dinner
1972 October 16 Camp Hill, PA, Remarks, Cumberland County Republican Dinner
1972 October 16 Camp Hill, PA, Excerpts, Cumberland County Republican Dinner
1972 October 17 Alexandria, MN, Remarks, Supporting Phil Hansen and John Haaven
1972 October 17 Alexandria, MN, Excerpts, Supporting Phil Hansen and John Haaven
1972 October 17 Moorehead, MN, Excerpts, President's Team Rally
1972 October 17 St. Paul, MN, Excerpts, President's Team Rally
1972 October 18 New York City, NY, Remarks, Travel Industry Committee
1972 October 18 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Travel Industry Committee
1972 October 18 New York City, NY, Press Interview, Travel Industry Committee
1972 October 19 New York City, NY, Remarks, New York State United Nation Day
1972 October 19 New York City, NY, Press Interview, New York State United Nation Day
1972 October 19 New York City, NY, Press Conference, New York State Black Committee
1972 October 20 Philadelphia, PA, Remarks, Revenue Sharing Signing Ceremony
1972 October 20 Philadelphia, PA, Excerpts, Revenue Sharing Signing Ceremony
1972 October 23 Long Island, NY, Excerpts, Excerpts, Rallies for President Nixon
1972 October 24 Albany, NY, Statement, Obituary of Jackie Robinson
1972 October 24 Syracuse, NY, Excerpts, Rally for President
1972 October 24 Onieda County Airport, Excerpts, Rally for President
1972 October 26 Los Angeles, CA, Excerpts, Committee to Re-Elect the President
1972 October 27 New York City, NY, Press Conference, 2nd Ave. Subway
1972 October 27 New York City, NY, Remarks, 2nd Ave. Subway
1972 October 27 New York City, NY, Press Interview, after 2nd Ave. Subway
1972 October 31 Washington, D.C., Remarks, National Press Club
1972 October 31 Washington, D.C., Excerpts, National Press Club
1972 October 31 Washington, D.C., Q and A Session, following National Press Club
1972 October 31 New York City, NY, Remarks, Honoring Senator Roy M. Goodman
1972 October 31 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Brotherhood in Action Dinner
1972 November 1 New York City, NY, Press Conference, National Housing Program
1972 November 1 Queens, NY, Excerpts, Annual Queens County GGP Night
1972 November 2 Rhode Island, Excerpts, Campaign Appearance for J. Chafee
1972 November 3 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Get Out the Vote Re-Elect Nixon
1972 November 3 New York City, NY, Excerpts, State Campaign Swing in New York City
1972 November 6 Queens, NY, Press Conference, Get Out the Vote Re-Elect Nixon
1972 November 6 Upstate, NY, Excerpts, Campaign swing at Buffalo, Rochester. etc.
1972 November 7 New York City, NY, Remarks, Re-Elect the President
1972 November 13 Syracuse, NY, Town Meetings
1972 November 13 Syracuse, NY, Press Interview, Town Meetings
1972 November 13 Elmira, NY, Town Meetings
1972 November 14 New York City, NY, Remarks, Federation of Jewish Philanthropies
1972 November 14 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Federation of Jewish Philanthropies
1972 November 15 Oneida, NY, Town Meeting
1972 November 15 Olean, NY, Town Meeting
1972 November 17 Queens, NY, Town Meeting
1972 November 17 Queens, NY, Press Interview, after Town Meeting
1972 November 17 Queens, NY, Press Interview, with Gabe Pressman
1972 November 17 New York City, NY, Interview, with V.M. Berezhkor
1972 November 20 New York City, NY, Press Interview, before State Republican Committee
1972 November 20 New York City, NY, Remarks, State Republican Committee
1972 November 20 New York City, NY, Excerpts, State Republican Committee
1972 November 20 New York City, NY, Press Interview, after State Republican Committee
1972 November 21 Eastchester, NY, Remarks, Bill Butcher Testimonial
1972 November 21 Eastchester, NY, Excerpts, Bill Butcher Testimonial
1972 November 22 Lake Placid, NY, Town Meeting
1972 November 22 Buffalo, NY, Buffalo Town Meeting
1972 November 30 Syracuse, NY, Remarks, Stephen Roger Award
1972 November 30 Syracuse, NY, Excerpts, Stephen Roger Award
1972 November 30 Rochester, NY, Town Meeting
1972 December 1 Albany, NY, Remarks, Citations to National Guards
1972 December 4 Albany, NY, Statement, Selection of Warren Anderson as Senate Majority Leader
1972 December 13 New York City, NY, Remarks, Traffic Safety Council
1972 December 13 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Traffic Safety Council
1972 December 14 Albany, NY, Remarks, Testimonial Dinner for Earl Brydges
1972 December 14 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Earl Brydges Testimonial Dinner
1972 December 15 Albany, NY, News Conference, in Red Room at State Capitol
1972 December 29 Albany, NY, Swearing-in Judges
1973
1973 January 3 Albany, NY, Annual Message to Legislature
1973 January 4 New York City, NY, Interview, Tom Plate New York Magazine